http://www.stickersgalore.com/articles/help/1521

0Hi there!Login My Account
Hi there!Login | Create an Account0Current Promo Codes
newnew productsback in stockcoming soonpre-order|clearance|brandDoodlebugKaiserCraftPaper HouseSports SolutionA Cherry On TopDoverKaren FosterPaper House ProductionsSRM PressACOTDritzLittle BPebbles Inc.StampendousAmerican CraftsEcho ParkLittle Yellow BicyclePet QwerksStamping StationAmy TangerineEK SuccessMaggie HolmesPhotoplaySticko StickersAveryElizabeth Craft DesignsMark RichardsPink PaisleeTim HoltzBella BlvdExpress Yourself MIPMaya RoadPinkfresh StudioTPC StudioBo BunnyEyelet OutletMe & My Big IdeasPioneerTrend EnterprisesCarta BellaFancy Pants DesignsMomentaPrimaTrends InternationalChickaniddy CraftsGlitz DesignMoxxieQueen & CoTrimcraftCrate PaperGraphic 45Mrs GrossmanRangerUniversity GamesCreativity StreetHeidi SwappMrs. GrossmansReminisceWe R Memory KeepersDamask LoveIt Takes TwoMultiCraft ImportsRuby Rock-ItWincraftDariceJillibean SoupMy Minds EyeSandylionWoodland ScenicsDear LizzyJoleesOneCanoeTwoSimple StoriesZva CreativedocraftsK and CompanyP13Smoothfoam|themeAlphabetDessertsGift IdeasNature & OutdoorsSpringAnimalsDinosaursGirlsNauticalSt. Patricks DayAnniversaryDisneyGolfNBAStarsAutumnDisney FrozenGraduationNFLSummerBabyDisney Mickey & FriendsGymnasticsNHLSwimmingBaby BoyDisney Pooh & PalsHalloweenNickelodeonTeacherBaby GirlDisney PrincessHeartsNumbersTeenBaseballDogsHockeyPartyThank YouBasketballDora The ExplorerHomecoming & PromPatrioticThanksgivingBeachDragonfliesHomemakingPetsTrainsBeerEasterHorsesPhrases & SayingsTransportationBirds & OwlsFairiesHuntingPicnic & BarbequeTravel & VacationBirthdayFamilyKaratePirateTropicalBowlingFarmKidsPolice & FireUnicornsBoysFarmhouseKitchenPregnancyUS DestinationsBugs & InsectsFashionLove & RomancePrincessValentines DayButterfliesFathers DayMedicalRainbowVintageCalendarFishingMedievalReligiousVolleyballCamping & HikingFlamingosMemorialRound & Oval LabelsWeatherCatsFloralMenRunningWeddingChalkboardFoodMermaidsSailingWesternCheerleadingFootballMilitarySchoolWineChristmasFourth of JulyMLBSea LifeWinterCoffeeFriendshipMonstersSoccerWinter SportsConstructionFruitMothers DaySoftballWorld DestinationsCraftsGamesMovingSpaceWrestlingCruiseGardenMusicSportsZoo & SafariDance & Stage|hot|gift certificates|promo codes
Privacy statement
General Privacy Statement
This privacy policy sets out how StickersGalore.com, a subsidiary of Stickers Galore Inc, uses and protects any information that you give when you use this website.
StickersGalore.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
StickersGalore.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to view these changes.
You may visit StickersGalore.com and use our resources without revealing any information about yourself. and agree to our Web Site Agreement. The only personal data that is required to obtain an account is your name and e-mail address.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
Name
Contact information including email address
Demographic information such as postal code, preferences and interests
Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
Personal Information
When you place an order at StickersGalore.com, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number and expiration date. Giving us your phone number is optional -this will help if we have any questions or need to contact you about your order.
We are committed to protecting your privacy. We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. Our cookies are used primarily for the convenience of our customers.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Email
The email address you provide for order processing may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order. If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, promotions, etc. However, you may opt-out at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe link in the email.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. When you place orders with us, we use a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. All of the customer data that we collect is protected against unauthorized access.  In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.  Credit card information is not stored online nor do we keep a copy of it at our offices. Stickers Galore is PCI DSS compliant. Stickers Galore is tested daily by TrustGuard to verify Hacker Safe status.
CUSTOMER SERVICEContact UsHelp CenterShippingReturnsMy AccountNewsletter Sign UpABOUT USOur StoryMeet the TeamAffiliatesCareersTerms & ConditionsPrivacy PolicyLET'S CONNECTCopyright © 1997-2020, Stickers Galore, All Rights ReservedLoading
